# Pallavi Jayaraman | Content Writer and Marketer

As a content writer, I have had the opportunity to research, write, and publish content for products and marketing. My goal is to reach out to maximum readers, convey thoughts and provide information in the easiest way.

pallavijayaraman@gmail.com (+91) 7829124275

# **EXPERIENCE**

### Design Esthetics, Bengaluru- Content Writer

July 2022- Feb 2023

- Social Media Copies
- Website Copies
- Infographic Content
- · Articles for various Clients
- Ad Copies
- YouTube Descriptions
- Blogs

# PNJXN, Bengaluru —Content Writer and Marketing Executive

Aug 2021 - Mar 2022

- Researched and created content for client's social media presence
- Worked one on one with clients to understand their content needs and goals.
- Created website content that reflected client's ideals and offerings
- Writing newsletters for various clients
- Writing content for infographics
- Writing and publishing blogs for various clients

#### Accenture, Bengaluru — Operations Associate

March 2018 - June 2019

- Assisting with monitoring and tracking incidents to ensure resolution occurs within the Customer Service Level Agreement.
- Predominantly Voice Interaction support and sometimes email.

## IBM, Bengaluru — Technical Support Associate

Mar 2017 - Nov 2017

- Providing dependable and timely resolution to all product-related technical issues experienced by customers.
- Providing remote Infrastructure support delivery and performing problem cause analysis

# SKILLS

Creative Writing, Social Media Marketing, Content Marketing,

#### TOOLS

Semrush, Meta Business Suite, Mailchimp, Hootsuite

### LANGUAGES

English, Hindi

### **EDUCATION**

B. Tech, Computer Science and Engineering: VTU Belgaum, May 2016

12th: CBSE

10th CBSE